I've met thousands of Fascinating People
and I have some wonderful memories but
if you'd like to leave your loved ones
more than happy memories you might want
to look at this the AXA sunlife
guaranteed over 50 plan it's the most
popular plant of its type in the UK from
only £6 a month it pays a fixed cash
some When You're Gone which could help
towards funeral costs or be left as a
cash gift if you raed 50 to 885 you're
guaranteed to be accepted with no health
questions it's that straightforward as
long as you keep paying the premiums the
full cash sum is payable on death after
you've had the plan for 2 years for full
details call 868 50 your first month's
premium is free and you get a welcome
gift you receive a free par a pen just
for inquiring you'll be in good company
with a guaranteed over 50 plan so why
not call today on 800 68050 or visit
over50 plan. co.uk